finmde.com 2017-04-29

# Privacy Notice : finmde.com, win 7 key finder - finmde.com

Thank you for accessing the website. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read our Privacy Notice.

This Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information. This privacy notice also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Notice explains your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting our website, you accept the practices described in this notice.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION:** We collect information from you in several different ways on this website. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

  * Help make this website easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * Help you quickly find information, products, and services.
  * Help us create content on this site that is most relevant to you.
  * Help you to new information, Windows 7 Key products, and services that we offer.

**ORDERING:** To protect your privacy information, we do not collect your certain personal information. You can buy your favorite items on our website via PayPal, and once we receive the payment inform we'll process order quickly for you.

Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned! Any information you provide will be held with the most care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.

If we change or upgrade this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this website so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this privacy notice from time to time so you will know if the privacy notice has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Notice, please contact us.

Back To [Windows 7 key store](http://www.finmde.com/) Page!  
---
